Bonus Short Stories

Elemental ☆ Teacher, Professor Celia! (Happy New Year Edition!)

Somewhere on Earth...

Celia Claire was a foreign teacher that had relocated to work as a substitute teacher in a Japanese high school.

However, it was January 1st — New Year’s Day. High schools in Japan were all on break, so Celia decided to go and gain some cross-cultural experience by way of the Japanese New Year.

At present, she was waiting at a dry riverbed for two of her high school students to show up.

“Hey, Suzune. Are you sure I don’t look weird?” she asked Endo Suzune, the primary school girl standing beside her. Suzune was also waiting for the two high school students who had yet to arrive.

“You’re fine. Even my mom was talking about how good it looks on you!” Suzune gave her stamp of approval with wide, beaming grin.

“If you’re sure, then...” Celia checked her outfit restlessly. She was currently wearing what would be considered the pride of Japan’s traditional clothing — a long-sleeved kimono. On top of that, she held a hagoita with a cute design in her hand. Next to her, Suzune was also wearing a kimono and holding a hagoita of different designs.

The hagoita were wooden paddles to be used in a game of hanetsuki — similar to badminton — and they were about to meet up with the other two people to play it. Suzune’s mother had highly recommended wearing kimono for hanetsuki, so they had spent a long time rummaging through the wardrobe before reaching this point.

“Ah! Haruto onii-chan, Miharu onee-chan!” When Suzune noticed the arrival of the two people they were waiting for, she ran over to them energetically.

“Happy new year, Suzune. Be careful not to run in such pretty clothes,” Amakawa Haruto warned her with a faint smile. Beside him stood another high school student, Ayase Miharu, who was smiling pleasantly at Suzune.

“H-heh! H-Happy New Year!” Suzune blushed as she bowed her head at Haruto. At that point, Celia had caught up to them.

“Happy New Year, Professor Celia. The kimono looks very pretty on you,” Haruto said in greeting.

“O-Oh, yeah. T-Thank you. And happy new year... You too, Miharu.” Celia’s cheeks reddened with embarrassment.

“Happy New Year to you, Professor Celia, Suzune,” Miharu returned the greeting with a graceful bow.

Incidentally, Haruto was in his casual clothes while Miharu was dressed in a long-sleeved kimono, hagoita at the ready.

“You’re so beautiful, Miharu... This must be what they call a Yamato Nadeshiko,” Celia said, completely captivated by Miharu’s beauty. In reality, her glossy black hair and delicate aura made the perfect pair to the Japanese clothes.

“N-No, not at all. If anything, your white hair suits your kimono so well, you look like a beautiful illusion, Professor Celia,” Miharu said in a high-pitched voice, blushed shyly.

“Ahaha, thank you. I’d like to believe that... and Suzune, you can snap out of it already!” Celia thanked her with a faint smile before she noticed Suzune acting strangely beside her.

“Ehe, ehehe, Haruto onii-chan called me pretty...” She was extremely pleased about being complimented by her beloved Haruto.

Celia sighed tiredly. “Geez...” But the corners of her mouth were twitching up in a smile.

Miharu laughed in amusement. “Ahaha, shall we begin soon?”

“Yes, but I don’t know the rules of hanetsuki very well...”

“The rules are that there are basically no rules. You hit the shuttlecock towards another person and continue doing that until you stop. Do you want to try it with me first?”

“Yes, please.”

Thus, it was decided that Miharu and Celia would play first against each other.

“Okay. Suzune, how about we stand a little further back and observe them?”

Haruto took Suzune by the hand and urged her to move a short distance away.

“Fweh?! O-Okay!”

With a bright red face, Suzune agreed. And watching the two of them —

“Hmph...”

— were Miharu and Celia, both looking a little envious.

I’ll show you the maturity of an adult!

This is a story that occurred just after Rio and Aishia took Celia away from the capital of Beltrum.

“Shall we go, Aishia?”

“Yeah.”

Rio picked Celia up in a princess carry and rose into the air, gently, with his wind spirit arts.

“Ah...”

Celia felt the faint floating sensation and tightened her grip around Rio reflexively.

Seeing Rio all grown up, reliable and warmhearted, filled her with relief. Feeling it first-hand made Celia so happy, she squeezed her arms even more.

“Fufu,” Celia let out a giggle without realizing.

“Are you scared, Professor?” Rio asked, looking down at Celia’s face; he had noticed how Celia’s grip around him had strengthened. Their eyes met at a nose-to-nose distance away from each other.

Celia couldn’t help the flush that crept over her face. “...N-Nope, I’m not scared. Aishia carried me through the air earlier, so I’m used to the floaty feeling now,” she replied, averting her gaze shyly.

Belatedly, she realized that being in a princess carry had put her at a much closer distance to Rio than she thought.

Very belatedly.

“That’s good, then. If you’re scared, just give me a heads up. I’ll adjust my speed for you,” Rio offered, tilting his head a little curiously.

“O-Okay.” Celia nodded awkwardly.

I-I felt so elated when we were departing, I asked Rio to carry me for the flight... Would it have been more natural to ask Aishia instead? No, but Rio agreed so casually... I-It was natural, right? she thought to herself.

Her heart thudded louder and louder in her chest. When she peered up at Rio’s face in wonder, she saw that he didn’t seem to be as nervous — or rather, nervous at all — compared to her.

Maybe I’m thinking too much about it? Yes, this much is n-normal. Normal. That’s right, I have to be carried all the way to the kingdom of Galarc, so this is necessary. There’s nothing strange about it.

Celia pondered to herself as she watched Rio’s expression carefully. That’s right — since Aishia was the one to carry her out of the capital, now it was Rio’s turn to do the carrying. That was the natural flow of things, wasn’t it?

That’s right. I’m clinging to him because it’s necessary, so it would be weird if I acted really nervous about it. I’m Rio’s teacher, so I must show him the maturity of an adult woman. I’ll show him he’s not the only one that’s grown up!

Right. The reason why she was being held in a princess carry was because it was easier to move with. There was nothing weird about it. Celia’s thoughts spiralled in a clearly childish way.

“...Professor, you seem a little restless. Are you scared after all?” Rio asked as he checked on Celia’s expression.

“N-Not at all. I’m fine, I’m mature, I can handle this much. You can even go faster if you want!” Celia feigned composure as she replied. She made to loosen her hold around Rio too.

“Really? Then...” Rio said with amusement, raising his speed in a sudden burst of intensity.

“Hyahn!” The sound had escaped from Celia unconsciously. She threw her arms tightly around Rio in a panic.

“See, it’s dangerous. Make sure you hold on properly,” Rio chuckled, adjusting his hold on her.

As a result, they were even closer together than they were before. Celia buried her face into Rio’s neck and, after a pause, blushed bright red.

Celia scolded Rio in shock. “Y-You’re a bully, Rio! I’ll have you know that was a sound of surprise just now, not fear. Got it?!”

“Ahaha, sorry,” Rio apologized with a laugh.

Aishia nodded with satisfaction as she flew next to them. “Cute.”

Chapter 3: Shopping

The morning after Rio had spent his first night with Celia and Aishia...

After finishing their breakfast, Rio and the others headed towards Amande. Their destination was the headquarters of the Ricca Guild in order to purchase daily necessities for Celia.

The stores all over the city had begun their business at a rather early hour of the morning, filling the roads with a lively crowd of merchants and customers.

“This is Amande. Like you’ve heard, it’s a very busy and bustling city.”

From under her hooded cloak, Celia looked at all the stalls lining the road with great interest in her eyes.

“First, let’s go buy you clothes at the Ricca Guild. Professor, make sure you don’t get separated...” Rio suggested.

“Let’s hold hands.” Aishia grabbed Rio’s left hand with complete familiarity.

“...I see. Then, may I hold your right hand?” Celia glanced up at Rio’s face and sought his permission shyly.

“Of course. Please, allow me.” Rio nodded readily, taking Celia by the hand.

“Y-Yeah...” H-He seems quite used to this, Celia thought to herself with a start, squeezing Rio’s hand nervously in return.

After that, the three weaved their way through the crowds and made their way to the Ricca Guild’s store — it was the branch that specialized in women’s clothing that he had taken Miharu to before. Celia’s heart was leaping at the thought of going shopping for the first time in a while, her steps springy with happiness.

When they stopped in front of the building. Rio turned to address the two girls. “Okay. I’m going to go a different way for a while. If you need anything, just tell Aishia — I’ll return right away with our telepathic connection.”

“Got it. See you, Haruto.” Celia nodded cheerfully, using Rio’s alias out loud. They had decided in advance that they would call Rio “Haruto” while outside in public, where other people could possibly overhear them, since Rio’s arrest warrant was still active, even now.

“Take care of Cecilia, Aishia,” Rio said, using Celia’s alias.

Since Celia was also technically abducted to the public, she couldn’t afford to walk around without some form of disguise, either — hence the use of an alias. On top of that, Celia’s silver hair had also been changed to blonde with the same artifact that Rio used to change his hair.

“Leave it to me.” Aishia nodded quietly but firmly.

“I will. See you later.” Rio nodded contently, turning on his heel.

After he had disappeared into the crowds, Celia lowered the hood of her cloak and turned to Aishia. “Let’s go inside, shall we?”

“Okay.” Aishia nodded, lowering her hood, too. The two of them entered through the doors.

“Now, let’s start from the first floor and make our way up. Will you help me choose, Aishia?” Celia said to Aishia in a lively voice.

“Sure,” Aishia agreed readily.

Thus, the two began their long shopping spree. Like Celia had declared, they went through each floor in order. The building had four floors total: the first through the third were for clothes and small accessories, while the fourth was entirely dedicated to lingerie.

“Oh, there’s so much variety to the Ricca Guild’s clothing. The real thing really is different. Everything catches my eye.” Celia giggled, choosing clothes from everywhere.

She was comparatively more of the secluded type, but when it came to shopping, she would pick clothes she liked with skilled hands. Furthermore, she also wasn’t wasteful, so she checked every price tag carefully as she went.

The two beautiful girls clearly stood out, drawing the attention of the store attendants and other customers.

“How about this?” Celia showed each piece to Aishia one by one, seeking her opinion. In return, Aishia gave precise advice with consideration for Rio’s tastes in mind.

“Haruto would like the other one better.”

If Rio were here, he probably would have asked “How do you know my preferences?” with a twitch in his smile. “I see, I see. I think I’m starting to get a good idea of Haruto’s tastes. I’ll keep this one instead, then.” Celia nodded with satisfaction.

After that they moved to the next floor and chose several good-looking pieces, then headed to the fourth floor to choose underwear. “Okay, now that I’ve noted all the regular clothes I want, let’s go to the lingerie section first.”

Celia climbed the stairs happily, but she stopped mid-step.

“...H-Hey... You wouldn’t happen to know Haruto’s taste in underwear too, right?” she asked fearfully.

“I don’t. We’ve never selected underwear together.” Aishia shook her head quietly.

The reason why she was so knowledgeable of Rio’s tastes was now clear: the second time they had come shopping here with Miharu, they had actually went clothes shopping together. Aishia clearly remembered Rio’s comments from when Miharu asked him for his opinion.

“I-I see...” Celia sighed in relief. She felt an indescribable mix of relief and disappointment.

“But...” Aishia murmured. Celia froze, on high alert.

“Huh?”

“He probably doesn’t like them to be too flashy,” Aishia predicted, making Celia gulp.

“...W-Why?”

“Based on his clothing preference.”

“A-Ah. Well, that’s true... O-Okay then, fine. Let’s choose some,” Celia agreed with her heart racing in her chest, hurrying up the stairs with quick steps. Aishia silently followed her.

“Wow, there’s so much variety here. The Beltrum branch had a low number of selections and always sold out. With all of this, someone fla-... someone my size should be able to find underwear, too.” Celia’s eyes sparkled with a burning fire as they stepped into the lingerie shop.

“You can choose anything you want — That’s why Haruto brought you here.” Aishia explained.

In reality, the products by the Ricca Guild — especially the items for women — were of such a good quality, the products by other merchants couldn’t hope to compare.

And so, with approval from Miharu, Aki, and Masato, Rio held the ironclad belief that if one was to go shopping in the Strahl region, then it had to be at Amande.

After Miharu and the others learned to read and write, they had noticed how some Japanese names were mixed in among the products of the Ricca Guild’s stock. There was quite a bit of mystery there for them, but that was a story for another time.

“Fufu... Then I’ll have to be more grateful towards Haruto. Now, let’s pick some right away. We can start buying some good underwear.” Celia seemed extremely happy as she started to select underwear with a beaming smile. With light footsteps, she scoured high and low for lingerie, Aishia in tow.

“Thank you for your continued patronage. If you require any assistance or would like to have your companion’s size measured, please let me know,” a shop attendant offered, bowing her head at Aishia.

“Oh, then may I take you up on that offer? But wow, you come here often enough to be remembered?” Celia accepted the attendant’s offer before turning to Aishia.

“I’ve only been here twice,” Aishia replied.

“You’re so beautiful, you left an especially strong impression, Miss. The company you had last time was beautiful too, and you’ve brought another beauty along today,” the attendant added with a smile, looking at Celia.

Celia smiled shyly. “Ahaha, I see. Thank you for the compliment,” she said politely.

“We’re here to buy her underwear today, so I’m fine,” Aishia said to the attendant, getting her to measure Celia’s size.

“Understood. Then, shall we get to measuring right away?”

“Yes, please do.” Thus, Celia had her body measurements taken by the store attendant.

“Now, please come this way.” After being led to a private room that also acted as a changing room, Celia’s stripped down to her underwear and had her chest size measured.

“Your skin is very beautiful. You have such a lovely figure, too — I am most envious as another woman.” The attendant stared at Celia’s skin raptly as she measured her.

“Ahaha, it’s just a childish stature,” Celia said with a self-deprecating grimace, making the attendant shake her head firmly.

“That’s not true. You may have a petite body, but you also have curves where it matters. It’s a very feminine body shape.”

“...Ahaha, thanks.” Celia smiled uncomfortably.

After that, the size measurements wrapped up quickly and Celia was able to try on several attractive pieces of underwear.

◇　◇　◇

Meanwhile, Rio moved about on his own, gathering information from the inner city.

His goal was information about the heroes who could be the friends and family of Miharu, Aki, and Masato, but he was also looking for the whereabouts of Lucius, the mercenary who murdered his mother. He walked around the market, visiting inns that were open for lunch and chatting up shopkeepers as he ordered.

It’s no different from last time. The heroes, that man... There’s no new information circulating... Rio left the inn he was gathering information at and sighed quietly. According to what Celia had told him, the Galarc Kingdom also had a spirit stone that could summon a hero, but there was still no identifying information about that hero as of yet. The only things circulating were witness accounts of what was most likely the pillar of light that occurred during a summoning rising from the Galarc castle. It was possible that different kingdoms controlled the flow of information differently, Rio guessed.

If it’s come to this, then maybe I should sneak into the castle of each kingdom? It isn’t impossible with Aishia’s cooperation, but... it’s a little risky. The situation was very different compared to Celia’s case, after all.

I’ll need connections to try the head-on approach... And it has to be that of a rather powerful noble. Though there’d still be risks...

The head-on approach seemed like it’d be a headache, too — after all, he had already experienced the mess that was royal and noble society first hand.

Rio pondered and pondered, ending with a great sigh. For now, my first goal is to confirm the full names of all the heroes across the kingdoms. If I can find that by gathering information in town, fine. Even if I have to sneak into the castle, I mustn’t be greedy. Direct contact should be left as a second priority goal. As long as I can gather their existence and location, at the very least...

He decided to think about how to approach them another time. It was only delaying the issue until later, but there was time.

In any case, he had to consider living with Celia from now on, too. Although he had promised to teach her various things about sorcery and spirit arts, he at least didn’t have to teach her a language like he had with his Japanese guests.

All that was left was —

Lucius...

Rio recalled his vow to avenge his mother and grit his teeth. This man was probably a more difficult task to deal with than handling Miharu, Aki, and Masato.

I’ve got as far as how he became the leader of a famous mercenary squad as an adventurer, but his name hasn’t come up at all in recent years. The mercenary squad he was affiliated with — the “Lions of the Sky” — was widely known in certain regions of the Strahl region, but there was absolutely no information as to where he was located.

Is he dead?

When Rio imagined it, an indescribable emotion rose within him, making him frown.

He didn’t care if he was dead, but Rio’s resentment wasn’t so shallow that he could accept his life or death status as unknown. The flames of revenge that burned quietly in the depths of his heart had yet to extinguish, even with his reunion with Miharu and Celia.

Rio squeezed his hand into a fist.

...I should look into it a little further.

He quieted his heart with a deep breath and started walking again.

◇　◇　◇

Roughly one hour later, Rio was done gathering information and now stood next to Aishia in front of a changing room on the second floor of the Ricca Guild.

“Hey, what do you think?” Celia twirled around in front of Rio and Aishia, wearing the clothes she was trying on. The hem of the skirt fluttered softly.

Chapter 7: Ambush

After that, Liselotte’s party continued to clatter along in their carriages, ignorant of Reiss’ presence above them. They proceeded through the deep woods towards Amande. The front carriage where Liselotte and the others were riding had been filled with incessant chatter for some time now.

“...So I shut myself away in my room that day, reading two whole books before I knew it. When I finally came out in the evening, my sister was very exasperated with me,” Flora was saying happily.

“Fufu, you sure must like reading,” Liselotte interjected with a smile.

“Yes!” Flora agreed happily.

Liselotte looked at Flora’s expression. So it isn’t that she’s bad at talking after all. When she came to my estate last time, too, she responded properly whenever I asked her something... she thought, analyzing Flora. Rather than being bad at speaking, Flora was probably just shy. While that was part of the reason why she didn’t speak much, Hiroaki’s enthusiastic bragging about himself probably didn’t help with allowing Flora the chance to speak, either.

In that regard, Roanna was a much better listener in how she cleverly made Hiroaki feel good about his chattering. Her difference in personality to Flora was clear.

“Ah, well I’ve read eleven books in a day before,” Hiroaki boasted.

Liselotte widened her eyes in a show of amazement. “Why, that is amazing.”

“As one would expect from Sir Hiroaki. With that speed of reading, you could put a great amount of information into your head...” Roanna looked at him with reverence.

“Well, even I can’t read technical books at that speed, but if it’s popular fiction produced for entertainment, then I’ve read most of the ones produced in my world. I just forget myself and lose time reading,” Hiroaki said smugly.

“Umm, I can’t read that fast, but I think I understand. I find myself completely immersed in the world of the story when I’m reading fictional novels, too...” Flora offered hesitantly. She seemed to find it easier to join the conversation when it was about topics that interested her.

Liselotte giggled, smiling. “I would love it if the two of you could tell me a little more about the worlds you’re so immersed in and what you’re thinking about when you read,”

“Oh?” A thought seemed to occur to Hiroaki, making him grin happily.

“...The world I was in, you say?” Flora’s eyes rounded in surprise.

“Yes. If you don’t mind, will you tell me about it?” Liselotte asked, peering at Flora’s face closely.

“Umm, I read novels while thinking of myself as the mirror opposite of the main character in the story. The main character that has something I don’t have moves around in a world I don’t know about. As I wonder about what the main character might be thinking or what kind of actions they will take, my mind gets more and more immersed until it feels like I’m in the world of the story, experiencing all the emotions...” Flora said, looking a little embarrassed.

“Ah, I think I get it. There aren’t many good works out there that can make you think that way, though. Most have such rough backgrounds and development that they cannot achieve that,” Hiroaki lamented.

“Then the world Sir Hiroaki speaks about is...” Liselotte began to ask, when suddenly —

“S-Stop the carriage! Monsters are in the area! Everyone, prepare for combat!” Aria’s yelling voice could be heard from outside. One beat later, the carriage came to a stop.

“Whoa, what’s going on?!” Hiroaki’s body shook as he looked around the carriage in confusion.

◇　◇　◇

Moments before notice of the monster attack reached Liselotte’s carriage, Aria walked in front of the carriage with Liselotte and the others inside, surveying the forest with her sharp eyes.

...That’s strange. It’s too quiet.

“What’s the matter, Aria? You seem kind of tense. Do the gazes of the knights bother you?” Cosette, who was walking next to Aria and noticed her sharp look, called out to her.

The current positions of the squad were as follows: Aria and the other female attendants were escorting the front of Liselotte’s carriage, Stewart and Alphonse each took a side to the left and right of both carriages with most of the knights, while Duke Huguenot’s carriage was protected from the rear by commanding officer Raymond and several other knights.

“No, that’s not it.” Aria shook her head with a sigh.

“But... can’t you feel them looking?” Cosette said with a happy giggle.

“They just find it curious to see women holding weapons,” Aria answered flatly. Compared to the armed knights, the attendants looked distinctive in their uniforms with weapons equipped. Among them, Cosette particularly stood out by carrying her halberd.

“Well, I’m sure that’s part of it, but wouldn’t you get used to seeing that pretty quickly? I think they’re actually entranced by my beauty. What do you think?” Cosette said proudly. In reality, her appearance was far above that of an average person.

“Then wouldn’t the attention gather on you more than Aria?” Natalia said exasperatedly from where she was walking nearby.

“S-Shut up. Aria’s face is too perfect and cold. Someone cuter like me is much better. Right, Chloe?” Cosette objected, turning to the trainee attendant walking beside her.

“Huh, me?! No, ah, umm...” Chloe looked between Aria and Cosette’s faces, at a loss for words.

“You don’t have to take her seriously, Chloe,” Natalie said with a sigh.

“Ah, okay. But I think everyone is all very beautiful,” Chloe offered hesitantly.

“Fufu, thank you. You’re a good girl, Chloe.”

Chloe’s cute, too, you know?” Natalie and Cosette both smiled happily. Chloe was taken aback and flushed red.

“N-No, that’s not true...”

Natalie and the others watched Chloe fondly. After a lull in conversation, Cosette turned to Aria.

“So anyway, you know the commanding officer of the knights? He was a little stuck up, but he’s handsome. Introduce him to me, Aria... Hm? You really are looking tense now. Is there something bothering you?”

Aria was looking at their surroundings with stern cautiousness. “...Don’t you think it’s a little too quiet?” she asked.

“Too quiet?” Natalie and Cosette exchanged a look before tilting their heads. Chloe also looked on in confusion.

“The forest. I can’t feel any of the heavy presences unique to monsters and beasts,” Aria elaborated.

“Presences... We haven’t been attacked by any monsters or beasts yet, but even they wouldn’t try anything against this many people, don’t you think?” Cosette said while glancing around.

Wild beasts were cautious creatures — Unless they were highly territorial, in their breeding season, or starving for food, they rarely attacked humans. In contrast to that, monsters were intelligent and aggressive beings. While they couldn’t speak, even the weakest monster — the goblin — could use simple equipment and swarm in groups to attack people. During the Divine War, goblins had served the Demon King’s army. For humans, they were vile and malicious creatures that were to be targeted for elimination.

“Aria’s senses are reliable, so it’s a little curious, but... Could it be possible they’re just keeping their distance from us out of caution?” Natalie offered.

“This area’s already under the jurisdiction of the Amande adventurer’s guild. If a group of monsters appeared, they’d be eliminated immediately. Ah, but maybe the monsters know that and hide away deep in the forest, building their strength instead,” Cosette joked.

Natalie’s face darkened with worry as she shivered. “...That would be terrifying. Have there been any reports recently of monster numbers dropping?”

“Mm... There was a report from the adventurer’s guild about two months ago that monster spawn rates were down a little, but it isn’t too rare to see that kind of fluctuation... Well, there is the case of the black demi-dragon, too, so we should look into it a little more once we get back to Amande,” Cosette said with a thoughtful look.

“You’re right — let’s do that. Hah, I don’t see any rest in our foreseeable future...” Natalie sighed, head drooping slightly.

“Ugh, don’t say that...” Cosette grimaced.

Aria remained alert as usual of their surroundings, when —

“S-Stop the carriage! Monsters are in the area! Everyone, prepare for combat!” she suddenly yelled, making the carriages come to a halt.

The attendants immediately responded by surrounding the carriage with Liselotte and the others, but the knights looked around dubiously. “What? Monsters? Where...?” Their lack of trust in Aria had caused them to react belatedly, naturally.

“There is an enormous number of monsters hiding in the forests to both sides of us! I don’t know how they closed in this far, but hurry and ready your shields!” Aria ordered in irritation. The knights on the outside ring protecting the carriage did as they were told, lifting their shields towards the forest with slightly sluggish movements.

“Guh!” An incredible number of stones were suddenly thrown their way, hitting the knights and carriage.

“Kyaah?!”

“Whoa, what’s going on?!”

Flora and Hiroaki’s yells could be heard from within the carriage.

“Magicae Murum.” The attendants held their hands out in the directions they were facing and all chanted a spell at the same time. Then, a spell formula appeared at their palms, the magic circle rising and transforming their magic essence into a transparent wall of energy.

Magicae Murum was, as its name implied, a magic spell that created a protective wall made of magic essence. This barrier could block outside attacks from reaching the occupants inside. Its defensive abilities were controlled by the essence and size of the area, and simply maintaining it consumed essence. Thus, it was unfeasible to kept up forever, limiting its usefulness but making it the perfect ability for catching up on what was going on, or buying time to organize. A situation just like this.

The magic barrier the attendant girls put up completely enshrouded the carriage with Liselotte and the others inside; all additional stones thrown at the carriage were deflected. However, there were still knights that were injured by the first few stones thrown. While most of the stones had been blocked by the shields, several knights were placing pressure against their injuries.

Stones were the most primitive form of long-ranged weaponry, but their force was not to be underestimated. An unarmored human could be rendered incapable of fighting in a single hit, depending on where the stones struck.

“Kuh! Make the heavily wounded step back. Knights, continue to hold your shields at the sides and prepare for the next attack! Don’t step out of formation heedlessly — preserve your essence! Duke Huguenot, please stay down inside the carriage!” The commanding officer of Duke Huguenot’s knights, Raymond, gave his orders from behind the line with a strained voice.

“You can leave the front carriage’s protection to us!” Aria yelled towards Raymond.

“...Understood! It’s entrusted to you, Aria!” Raymond agreed shamefully. There was a delicate pause before he had responded — although they had definitely discussed the division of roles in an emergency before departure, his pride as a knight felt a sense of objection at relying on women. The rain of stones paused temporarily, when the situation suddenly changed —

“Monsters on the road to the rear!”

“To the front as well!”

From the forest off to the sides, goblins and orcs swarmed onto the road before and after Liselotte’s party in a pincer attack. Their numbers were absolutely overwhelming.

“No way... One hundred, two hundred, three? Just how many are there...?” Cosette’s face stiffened.

“...Can monsters plan such an organized attack?” Natalie was also dumbfounded as she looked at the monsters spreading out before them.

“M-Monsters have appeared from the forests to the side!” Chloe yelled in a high-pitched voice.

Aria thought for a few quick seconds before speaking up. “...Lady Liselotte, this is an emergency. We will need to take down the magic wall in order to preserve essence against this extreme number of monsters. Please remain crouched down inside the carriage and do not step outside. The carriage walls should protect you from stones, at least.”

Liselotte’s reply came from within the carriage immediately. “Okay, got it!”

Aria looked at the attendants and relayed them a plan she had come up with on the spot. “You girls leave the defense to the knights and take out the monsters approaching the carriage from the sides — even if it kills you. I will handle the enemies up front. After I’ve launched my attack, release the barrier and begin your attack. Understood?”

“Yes, ma’am!” the attendants all agreed together. Aria nodded in return, then looked at the knights on the sides.

“Knights at the sides, I leave the defense of the carriage to you. Leave the offense to us!” she yelled. The knights that had been frozen at the countless monsters swarming before them all trembled with a flinch. Their faces seemed to be questioning what a simple waiting attendant could do, when Aria drew her sword from the sheath at her waist with her right hand. At the same time, she held her left hand out and chanted a spell,

“Magicae Displodo.”

“Ahaha, of course. But it’s only you right now, Professor, so there’s no need to hide it, right?” Rio gave a bright smile as he watched Celia in return.

“Ah... Oh, geez!” Celia’s blush reached its peak as she struggled for breath. Unable to look directly at Rio’s face, she looked downwards instead.

“Professor?” Rio inclined his head curiously, peering at Celia’s face.

“W-Wait! Just give me a minute! I have to silence my feelings first!” Celia waved her hands in a panic, trying to stop him from leaning in and getting a look at her face.

“...Yes?” Rio continued to tilt his head, but obeyed Celia for now.

“...Okay, done,” She said after a few deep breaths, looking up at Rio’s face. Belatedly noticing how they were still close enough to be hugging, she backed away slightly. She had been held in a bridal carry the entire way here, so it really was a rather belated realization.

That being said, being carried here was a necessity, and there was no need to be so close to each other right now. That difference was extremely important to Celia.

“Then, let’s head inside the house. Please, come this way. You too, Aishia — let’s go in.” Rio looked at Celia’s face and made sure she was all right, before turning on his heel to call out to Aishia and head towards the front door.

“Okay.” Aishia gave a short nod and followed Rio. Celia started walking forward hesitantly. Once the three of them entered the house, Celia looked around the open living space and widened her eyes.

“...I never imagined there could be such a pleasant living space inside a rock...”

“I can guarantee you that it’s comfortable to live in. Let’s get you changed first, shall we? We can’t have you remain in that wedding dress forever, now.”

“...Yeah. But... Do you have a change of clothes...?” Celia said, looking at Rio doubtfully. She had left the capital with nothing but the clothes on her back, so she didn’t have a change of clothes handy. Not to mention how they hadn’t stopped anywhere on the way here, as they wanted to put as much distance between the capital as possible, leaving them no time for shopping.

“Let’s see. We’ll definitely go shopping tomorrow, but for today, you can just...”

Rio stared at Celia’s stature closely.

◇　◇　◇

Rio changed from his overcoat and combat clothing into his usual casual wear and went about preparing tea in the living room. Some time later, Celia and Aishia finished changing in a different room and returned to the living room wearing comfortable dresses.

“Say, whose clothes are these?” Celia asked Rio and Aishia as she looked down at her completed outfit.

“They belong to one of the girls who was summoned along during the hero summonings. They lived in this house for a short while, so...”

The clothes that Celia was wearing right now were the ones that Miharu and the others had forgotten to take from the laundry when they moved to the spirit folk village. It was obvious at a glance that Miharu’s clothes wouldn’t fit Celia in terms of height and fit, so Rio had given her Aki’s clothes to try on.

It looks like Aki’s clothes are perfect for the Professor, just as I expected.

Rio couldn’t help but smile in amusement at how Celia could fit into the clothes of a middle school student.

“...Just out of curiosity, how old was the girl who owned these clothes?” Celia suddenly asked out of the blue.

“Umm... thirteen,” Rio answered after an awkward pause.

“And the other girl you mentioned?” Celia puffed up her cheeks a little.

“...Sixteen. Ah, is it a little small after all? Umm, Aki — that’s the girl’s name — is just about your height, Professor, so I thought it would work. If you’d like, I can prepare the other girl — Miharu’s — clothes instead...?” It was as clear as day that the clothes wouldn’t fit, but Rio tried to be considerate and offer anyway.

“I-It’s okay. Yeah, it’s okay... it’s okay, but... umm, i-it’s a little tight around my chest, maybe. Yes, just a little, tight... B-But it’s fine!” she refused in a shrill and upset voice, shaking her head. She’d realized that Miharu’s clothes wouldn’t fit her. Although, her criticism of the chest area of the clothing may have simply been for show...

“I see, around your chest...” The flow of the conversation naturally let Rio’s gaze towards Celia’s chest. Celia certainly did seem more feminine than Aki in that regard.

“G-Geez, don’t stare so much. I know they’re small, gosh! I’m sure you like big ones too, don’t you, Rio? Ugh...” Though she hadn’t exactly been ogled at, Celia’s face turned red and she hid her chest out of embarrassment. The woes of a young lady were complicated.

“Ahaha, that’s not true.” Rio shook his head with a strained smile.

“...H-Hmm. R-Really?” Celia’s eyes widened faintly as her interest was piqued by his response.

“Yes, I don’t believe a woman’s charms are decided by the size of her bust. You’re plenty charming, Professor, so please have more confidence in yourself,” Rio said, his answer a textbook response. However, he must have truly felt that way, as his words didn’t seem contrived.

For a moment, Celia blinked in a daze. “T-Thanks... Wait, what are we even talking about here? I-I’m sorry.” With a flustered thanks and apology, she smiled in relief. Rio also smiled shyly.

“That aside, which would you like to talk about first? The reason why I could communicate with the kids that were summoned along with the hero, or spirit arts and the Time-Space Cache? Or would you like a bath first?” he asked, awkwardly changing the subject.

“R-Right. Can we talk first, then? Since you’ve poured the tea and all already.” Celia nodded uncomfortably, on board with talking.

“Of course. Let’s sit down, then... You too, Aishia. Come to think of it, it’s been a long time since I’ve had tea with you, Professor.” Rio chuckled with a smile, inviting Celia to take a seat on the sofa, before serving the three of them tea.

“Yeah, that’s true. It brings back memories...” Celia nodded with a smile as she recalled those times, before her expression suddenly changed. “Ah, but is it really okay for you to tell me?”

Rio tilted his head in question. “What do you mean?”

“Umm, the stuff about spirit arts and the Time-Space Cache aside, you seemed to be thinking kind of hard about how to explain the reason why you could communicate, so it seemed like you didn’t really want to say...” Celia explained nervously.

“Ah, no, it isn’t that I don’t want to say it. It’s just that I need to prepare my heart and find the right words to do so. You’ll probably be surprised, Professor,” Rio said with a troubled expression.

“I’ll be surprised?” Celia inclined her head curiously.

“Yes. I’m going to tell you something that doesn’t sound believable by any logical means... But I am not lying. I don’t want to keep it a secret from you forever, Professor, so will you listen to what I have to say?” Rio stared directly into Celia’s eyes.

“...About the reason why you could communicate, right?” Celia said nervously, having noticed that the air around Rio had changed.

Rio nodded quietly. “Yes.”

“Okay. I’ll believe you.” Celia nodded simply, without any sign of doubt.

“Wasn’t that a little quick?” Rio’s eyes widened a little in surprise.

“Because it’s you, Rio. I’ll believe anything you have to say,” Celia said, then smiled in amusement.

“...Thank you very much.” Rio was a little uneasy, and yet he smiled happily. Though it was faint, Aishia was smiling gently, too. Then, after a moment, he spoke up abruptly.

“I have the memories of a version of myself from another life.”

“...The memories of yourself... from another life?” Celia’s eyes rounded slightly.

“They’re the memories of my past life, probably,” Rio supplemented.

“Memories... of your past life... Huh...” Celia looked dazed as she parroted Rio’s words back at him.

“...I guess it is hard to believe after all?” Rio asked timidly. As the concerned party, his senses were numbed into naturally accepting the fact, but any normal person would be more likely to find the statement delusional.

“Ah, no, that’s not it. I believe you. I believe you, and I’m not shocked... If anything, I can actually accept it so easily, I’m having trouble finding the words to explain why... Could you tell me a little more about it, for now?” Celia answered impatiently, pressing for more.

Rio widened his eyes and gently continued to speak. “...To start from the conclusion, the children who were summoned along with the hero happened to be from the same country and world that I lived in within my memories.”

“...So that’s why you were able to understand their words. But what did you mean by saying that they’re ‘probably’ the memories of your past life?”

“...There’s no way for me to tell if those memories are real, if they’re really my memories, if they are real, or if they’re simply the memories of another person.” There was only a subjective connection, and no objective connections at all. But because Rio was talking about himself from such a distant point of view and speaking so sadly, Celia raised her voice subtly, feeling some strange sense of resistance to what he was saying.

“That... may be true... But you really do have those memories, and the people who arrived were really from a world exactly the same as those memories, right?”

Rio nodded with a faint smile on his face. “...Yes. But whether those memories are mine or not does not matter right now. What’s more important is if this explains why I could communicate with them. What do you think?”

“I accept your reason about that, but...” Celia didn’t seem quite satisfied.

Rio grimaced at Celia’s reaction. “If I were to add one thing, these memories awakened within me shortly after I turned seven years old. As you know, Professor, I was an orphan in the slums until then,” he said, adding to his explanation.

“...That’s around when we first met, right?”

“Yes. Actually, the first time we met in the slums was just after I regained those memories. I was still in the middle of my confusion when you spoke to me.” Rio looked back on that time and spoke with nostalgia.

“R...Really... No wonder you’ve seemed like a really calm and intelligent child ever since we met. It was as though you weren’t actually younger than me... Ahh, I see. No wonder... So that was why. I see...” Celia’s eyes widened as though she had realized something.

“Is something the matter?” Rio tilted his head and asked.

“Ah, no, it’s just about the reason why I accepted your words about your previous life’s memories so easily. I think it’s because it explains why you were always so mature in the past.”

“I see... What did I seem like to you back then, Professor?” Rio asked somewhat curiously.

“How did you seem... Well, you were mature and kind of isolated from your surroundings, and it was like I couldn’t see the limits of your potential...? Ah, but once I started talking to you properly, we became friends quite easily, so I thought you were a nice and polite child.” Celia recalled the Rio from back then as she spoke.

“...Is that so? Then if my memories hadn’t reawakened, you may have had a different impression of me,” Rio said, grimacing with a guilty look.

“Really?”

“I would have been more bitter and twisted. Because I was rather naive in those memories, I think what you saw, Professor, was a result of adding that to my orphan self.”

“I... see... So your personality changed when your memories returned. But I’m a little interested in exactly what kind of child you were before your memories returned, too. You think if we met a little earlier, my impression of you would have changed, right?” Celia asked, peering at Rio’s face.

“...We probably wouldn’t have gotten along, honestly. I wouldn’t have replied properly if you asked me for directions, and I wouldn’t have tried to save Princess Flora.”

“Eh? R-Really?!” Celia’s eyes widened in shock.

“Yes. I was aggressive and didn’t trust other people. I believe I would have rejected your kindness, too, Professor.” His distrust of other people was still the same even today, however.

“Uh... B-But I wouldn’t have backed down! I would have been friends with that Rio, too,” Celia said eagerly, making Rio laugh with amusement.

“Ahaha.” It was all hypothetical, but with Celia, he may have been able to open his heart to her.

“I-It’s no laughing matter. I want to be friends with you no matter what, Rio!” Celia glared at him reproachfully.

“...Thank you very much. I’m glad we became friends, Professor.” Rio laughed happily.

“Y-Yeah,” Celia nodded with a blush, changing the topic to hide her embarrassment. “Wait, but how old was the Rio within your memories?”

Rio paused for a moment before answering the question. “In my memories... I was twenty years old.”

“T-Twenty... Which means... Huh? Wait a minute. Then mentally, this means you’re older than me, right? Because I was around twelve years old when we first met...” Combining the personality of a seven-year-old with the memories of a twenty-year-old didn’t mean that their mentality would combine to become a twenty seven years old. But, at the very least, his mental age was still older than Celia when they first met.

“Hmm... Is that so? Even though I may have merged with the memories and personality of myself as Haruto, I’m still mostly myself as Rio, so I’m more aware of my sixteen year old self as Rio right now, though I think the young part of me may be strongly influenced...” Rio cocked his head as he answered, smiling faintly.

“Is that, so. Well, I guess... that’s how it is?” Celia responded rather disjointedly. She had suddenly become nervous at the idea of someone she had thought was younger the whole time being older. And Rio was being oddly unperturbed about it all.

“I don’t normally pay attention to it, so I’m not sure myself. It’s not something that can be answered by just thinking it over, either... At the same time, I don’t feel anything strange if you call me by my past name, Haruto,” Rio said, laughing loudly.

“Your name was Haruto... Oh, I see. That’s why you chose it as your alias,” Celia realized with satisfaction.

“Yes. I figured it’d be easier to relate to than a completely unknown name.”

“Aishia called you Haruto as well. Oh, I’m sorry, Aishia — We’ve been completely conversing between ourselves,” Celia apologized to Aishia, who had been silently listening beside Rio.

“It’s okay. Now is the time for Celia to talk to Haruto. I’m a little sleepy anyway.” Aishia yawned cutely and shook her head.

“Ahaha, thank you,” Celia thanked Aishia, then turned to address Rio. “...She’s quiet, but she’s a really nice girl.”

Aishia sleepily leaned her head against Rio’s shoulder. “Yes, Aishia’s helped me out a lot.” Rio smiled with familiarity and nodded, but Celia’s eyes rounded with shock.

“S-So it seems. And she’s really cute and pretty, too,” Celia said in a strangely high pitched voice.

W-What?! Why has she suddenly started clinging to him so naturally?! While the smile from their conversation remained on her face, Celia’s thoughts nearly came to a screeching halt.

Rio detected the change in Celia’s expression. “Professor?”

“B-By the way, I heard some things from Aishia during the time we were waiting to meet up with you in the capital. About spirit arts, and the fact Aishia’s a spirit.” Celia snapped back to her senses and guided the conversation towards Aishia. She was afraid of directly asking why the two of them were sticking so closely together.

“Yes. How much did you hear from Aishia?” Rio asked calmly.

“Umm, that Aishia was your contracted spirit, and a little about the basic knowledge regarding spirit arts. I was worried about whether we’d be able to meet up properly back then, so I wasn’t able to really pay attention as I would have liked. Could you tell me more about that too? As well as about your relationship. What is a contracted spirit, anyway?” Celia narrowed her eyes as she emphasized the part about their relationship and questioned spirit arts and spirits in a way that couldn’t be avoided.

“Umm, how much do you know about spirits and spirit arts to begin with, Professor?” Rio felt a strange sense of vigor from Celia, making him reply a bit nervously.

As far as the Strahl region went, those two topics were not common knowledge. Reading a wide range of old literature would reveal books that dealt with the topic a little, but there was nothing that went into much detail.

“...I’ve known about the existence of spirits for a while. But I’ve only seen them mentioned in books, and never imagined them to actually exist. Aishia looks like a normal girl to me, so she doesn’t really seem like it.”

“In other words, you don’t have much background knowledge about spirits nor spirit arts, but you’re willing to believe that she’s a spirit?”

“Well, she did turn into her spirit form while we were waiting for you outside the capital. It didn’t seem like a spirit art that could simply turn her invisible... So I had no choice but to believe what I was seeing,” Celia said, sighing tiredly.

“I see. Then, to start with a simple explanation of spirits first, spirits are incorporeal forms of mana with a sense of self.”

“...Mana?”

“Unlike ode... or magic essence, which is life energy, would it be easier if I told you to imagine mana as the natural energy that’s simply hanging in the air? Both sorcery and spirit arts manipulate essence to interfere with mana and create world-altering phenomena. That’s a point they have in common.”

“What is that? This is the first time I’m hearing it...” Celia made a dumbfounded face, though she seemed quite interested. Her thirst for knowledge had been activated.

“Unlike how sorcery relies on the spell formula to interfere with mana, spirit arts is characteristic by how the user directly interferes with mana. That relation means it’s easier to standardize the event of activating sorcery, and while spirit arts are more flexible in controlling events, it is harder to learn.”

“Would I be able to use spirit arts, too?”

“Yes. If you train, you can refine the skills in order to use spirit arts. However, you will need to remove all the spell formulas you have taken into your body through spell contracts.”

“Remove spell formulas from my body... You mean you can’t learn spirit arts if you acquire magic?” Celia questioned with wide eyes.

“Right. In order to interfere with mana, the user’s imagination and will plays an important factor, but if you have spell formulas within your body, they won’t be transmitted to the mana efficiently.”

“...Which means... wait a minute. Then... the reason you failed at all those spell contracts and were unable to acquire magic during your time at school was because using spirit arts made you unable to learn magic, or something? Were you failing on purpose?”

“That’s very astute of you... But not quite. The reason why I failed at the spell contracts and was unable to acquire magic was because I had a spirit contract with Aishia. At that time, I didn’t know anything about spirits or spirit arts.” Rio smiled softly, shaking his head as he spoke.

“So that’s where the spirit contract comes in... In that case, do you have to be contracted to a spirit to use spirit arts?”

“No, there’s no requirement for a spirit contract in order to use spirit arts. However, since the spirits are sublimated forms of mana, which is essential to the use of spirit arts, their harmony with spirit arts is excellent. As a result, the contracted user’s spirit arts affinity rises once a contract has been formed. On the other hand, the disadvantage is that contracting with a spirit means that spell contracts cannot succeed, making you unable to use magic.”

“...In other words, you’ve been contracted to Aishia since your school days? Then such intimacy... is understandable, I think?” Knowing that they had been contracted for so long made Celia boldly ask for the reason behind their intimacy. She pouted her lips a little, sulking.

“No... it seems like that, but Aishia has been asleep until only recently, and we were contracted without my knowledge too. I tried to ask her the reason, but it appears Aishia doesn’t have any memories from before she woke up...” Rio scratched at his head with a troubled expression, glancing at Aishia slumped against him.

“...Really?” Celia asked, looking between their two faces.

“Yes. According to an acquaintance that’s knowledgeable about spirits, Aishia’s rank as a spirit is high, but she’s a newly born spirit... Like a baby spirit, almost.”

“Hmm... Is that so?” Then the fact that Aishia was slumped against Rio may just be because she wanted to be doted on. Such a thought crossed Celia’s mind, but she didn’t voice it out loud to confirm it.

“Do you understand our relationship now?” Rio asked, watching Celia’s expression.

“Yeah, well... I guess.” Celia nodded somewhat reluctantly.

“Then next is the explanation about the Time-Space Cache, right?”

“There’s that too, but...”

“Is there something else bothering you?” Rio asked.

“Where did you get that knowledge and those magic artifacts from, Rio? You didn’t seem to know about spirits and things when you were at the academy, so I’m sure you learned about them after you left Beltrum, but...”

“Actually, on my way to the Yagumo region, I met some people that lived quietly, away from humans. They taught me many things. About spirit arts, about sorcery — their technology was far beyond what was available in the Strahl region — and while they had cut off all contact with outsiders, I was fortunate enough to be accepted as an acquaintance...” Out of consideration for the spirit folk, Rio spoke vaguely about their specific circumstances.

“I see... So that’s where you got the Time-Space Cache.” Celia read the room and chose not to pry too deeply about the identity of the people that Rio was referring to.

“Yes. They presented it to me as a symbol of our friendship.”

“You must really have their trust if they would give you such a bold and amazing artifact. Or is it something that can be easily made by those people?”

“No, it isn’t something that can be mass produced easily,” Rio said out of respect toward the spirit folk. He shook his head with a hint of a smile.

“I see... Umm... Then it wouldn’t be good to research it blindly after all, right?” Celia looked at Rio’s expression regretfully, thinking her earlier statement was careless.

“No, I don’t mind if you look at it. If there’s any knowledge you wish to acquire, I can tell you as much as I am able to. As long as you follow the condition of not spreading or circulating the knowledge you gain... But I’m sure you can be trusted with that, Professor.” Rio gave his ready assent, showing his strong trust in Celia.

“Uh... T-Thank you. If that’s the case, then I... I swear. I’m even willing to bind myself in a sorcery contract,” Celia said her thanks uneasily, giving her oath with a shy blush in her cheeks.

“I understand. Well, we can leave the troublesome rituals for later. Would you like to have a look now?” Rio said, reaching for his left arm with his right hand.

“...No. It’s a very tempting offer, but I’ll pass for now. There’s been so many shocking truths... I’m a little tired.” Celia shook her head with a strained smile.

“Oh, then how about a bath instead? It’ll help you relax,” Rio suggested.

“A bath! That sounds great...” Celia’s face brightened at once. She got close to Rio sitting directly opposite to her when Aishia’s sleepily relaxing form entered her field of vision. “...B-But could I relax a little more here? Watching Aishia being all sleepy has made me feel a little sleepy too. S-She looks pretty comfortable,” she said in a high pitched voice, glancing over at Aishia.

“Then, let’s decide what your room should be, Professor. There’s lots of space, so you can use whichever one you wish... but if you need a studio, then a bigger room would be better?” Rio replied with a cheerful suggestion. Celia pouted and stared fixedly at Rio’s face with a reproachful look, as though she was making an appeal.

“...Yeah, let’s,” she agreed a little gloomily after a moment.

Rio sensed Celia’s suspicious behavior and tilted his head in question. “Umm, is something the matter? Professor... Wait, Aishia?”

Aishia stood straight up, then briskly walked over to Celia and stopped in front of her.

“W-What?” Celia looked up at Aishia nervously.

“This way.” Aishia grabbed Celia’s hand and gently made her stand up.

“What?!” Celia raised a voice of objection in surprise, but Aishia continued to pull her hand.

“H-Huh?” Celia was made to sit down next to Rio. She let out a squeak; her recoil from being made to sit down had caused her to lean on Rio closely before she realized it. Seeing Celia like that, Aishia gave a single nod before sitting down on the opposite side, snuggling close to Rio like she had been earlier.

“The three of us should just go to sleep like this,” she suggested with Rio sandwiched in the middle.

Once she finally processed the situation, Celia’s face turned red. “Wh... Wh-Wh-What?!”

“C-Calm down, Professor!” Rio tried to appease the suddenly panicking Celia.

“W-What is this, what is this?!” With a bright red face, Celia questioned Aishia seated on the other side.

“You wanted to do this too, no?” Aishia replied bluntly.

Celia shook her head. “T-That’s! That’s...!” she yelled, feeling as though she was losing her mind.

“P-Professor, calm down! Look, take a deep breath.” Rio grabbed Celia’s shoulder and faced her. With that, Celia’s movements froze for a second, but meeting Rio’s eyes from point-blank range had Celia blushing even more.

“B-Baaath! No no no, I have to take a bath, a bath!” Celia stood up in a fluster, running out of the living room noisily.

“P-Professor?!” Rio called after Celia to stop her, but her footsteps showed no sign of ceasing. However, before long, Celia trudged back into the living room.

“...W-Where is the bathroom?” she asked, embarrassed.

“That’s...” Liselotte’s eyes widened.

“The Divine Arms owned by the heroes. I named mine Yamata no Orochi,” Hiroaki explained with a smug huff.

“Yamata no... Orochi.” Liselotte muttered its name.

“Oh, you have good pronunciation. Yamata no Orochi was a water god in the country I lived in. I gave it that name as it’s related to the power hidden in my Divine Arms. It takes the form of an eight-headed dragon, so it’s also called the dragon god.”

“Ooh...” Those present in the room raised their voices in awe, staring at the blade in Hiroaki’s hand. He seemed pleased by this.

“Well, I haven’t been able to try it at its full power yet, but its ability should live up to its name. It’s possible that the wannabe dragon nearby won’t stand a chance against it, either,” he said with a finishing pose, holding the sword at the ready.

Liselotte stared at Hiroaki’s blade intently before bowing her head quietly. “...In case the worst happens, I will rely on you, then.” Using an ability that had never been tested before in a real battle was dangerous, but she didn’t say that out loud.

“B-Baronet Bochsa! Excuse me!” A soldier of the city came running in a panic. Tension ran through the room, everyone imagining the worst.

“What happened?!” Baronet Bochsa asked immediately with a stern look.

“T-The dragon-like creature flew off towards the northern skies!” The soldier reported on the situation in a high-pitched voice.

“What...?” Baronet Bochsa’s expression showed faint shock before he turned his gaze to Liselotte, seeking her thoughts.

“...It may still be nearby. There’s also a possibility it will return. It’s still too early to think that the danger has passed. There will be no changes to the plan yet,” Liselotte offered calmly.

“It may be presumptuous of me, but I agree with Liselotte. It is still too early to relax. I believe it would be best to stay alert for several more weeks, at least,” Duke Huguenot agreed immediately.

“...You’re right,” Baronet Bochsa agreed with a tired expression.

“Ah, it’s just another stupid beast in the end. It can’t think for itself, so its actions are unpredictable. At any rate, there’s no changing my role of safely seeing Liselotte off. Leave that to me.” Hiroaki exhaled and shrugged his shoulders.

That night, Liselotte finished dinner and shut herself away in a guest room of Baronet Bochsa’s estate in order to prepare for their departure the next morning. At the moment, only Aria, her most trusted aide, was in the room with her.

“Hah...” Liselotte sighed heavily.

“Are you really okay with it?” Aria asked shortly.

“With what?“

“Having the hero’s company.”

“...I’m not really okay with it, but there isn’t much I can do about it. Though he may be a hero of another kingdom, I cannot speak against him too strongly. And judging by his personality, he would have come along even if I adamantly refused him,” Liselotte said with a tired expression, sighing once more.

“He does seem to be a rather willful person. Perhaps you caught his attention and interest? Congratulations,” Aria said, giggling in amusement.

“It’s no laughing matter...” Liselotte sulked and glared at Aria reproachfully.

“Well, forgive me, then. But wouldn’t this incident count as a favor for Duke Huguenot since you’re going along with the spoiled whims of the hero?”

“...That’s true. The duke seemed to think that way himself. That being said, from what I could see, that hero showed no signs of the mannerisms or aura characteristic of people of the military arts. I do not believe he has received proper combat training before.”

“He looked like he was completely unguarded to me too. And yet, that behavior was brimming with confidence. It didn’t seem like he was acting the amateur on purpose... Maybe the Divine Arms are just that amazing?”

“Recklessly handing an untrained person a powerful weapon is like asking for your allies to be injured,” Aria said with a darkened expression.

“...I’ll entertain him in the horse carriage while we’re moving. There’ll be quite the squad formed thanks to their knights accompanying us, so I doubt any bandits or the like would bother us. If a monster or beast attacks, you girls should coordinate with the knights to take care of them.”

“Understood. I can guess what you’re thinking, but leave it to us.”

“Yes, thank you. Well, we’ve already clearly defined the line of responsibility with them, so with regards to protection, we’ll rely on their accompanying knights as much as possible. There’s no need for our side to aggressively step into the frontlines,” Liselotte said, smiling tiredly.

“Your consideration is most appreciated. However, there were rumors several months ago of adventurers repeatedly going missing in the forests to the west of Amande. We must not let our guard down,” Aria warned Liselotte.

Liselotte placed a hand against her mouth and searched back in her memory. “Now that you mention it, there was a report like that. The disappearances suddenly stopped roughly two months ago, if I recall...”

“We dispatched a search party, but they weren’t able to deduce the cause of it all. A missing adventurer typically isn’t that rare of an incident, but we’ll be passing through that exact forest tomorrow, so I urge that you take care of yourself,” Aria said solemnly.

Liselotte thought for a moment. “...You’re right — I’ll keep that in mind. Thank you.”

◇　◇　◇

The next morning, Liselotte took her attendants and made their way to the garden of Baronet Bochsa’s estate. Hiroaki, Flora, and Roanna were yet to be seen in the garden, but Duke Huguenot’s knights had already gathered along with two horse-drawn carriages.

There were eight attendants, including Aria, Natalie, Cosette, and Chloe, whereas the Huguenot side had 26 knights — among them being Duke Huguenot’s eldest son, Stewart Huguenot, and Marquess Rodan’s second son, Alphonse Rodan.

“Liselotte, allow me to introduce you to the commanding officer and his assistants before we depart,” Duke Huguenot said once he’d spotted Liselotte. Stewart, Alphonse, and another male knight in his mid-twenties walked over. The latter stepped forward first.

“My name is Raymond Brandt. It is an honor as a knight to be able to escort a beautiful woman like you. Pleased to make your acquaintance, Lady Liselotte,” he greeted respectfully, kneeling before Liselotte in a pompous manner.

“It’s very nice to meet you, Mister Raymond.” Liselotte gracefully held the hem of her skirt and returned the greeting.

“The two young ones here are Brandt’s assistants, acting as the supervisors of the younger knights. While it is embarrassing to admit, we’re short on personnel. In order to have them gain experience, the younger knights have been proactively pushed to more assignments. First, this is Alphonse, Marquess Rodan’s son,” Duke Huguenot said.

“I’m Alphonse Rodan. It’s nice to meet you, Lady Liselotte.” Alphonse huffed with a smug smile and greeted proudly.

“Pleased to meet you, Mister Alphonse,” Liselotte returned the greeting brightly.

“And this is my son. You may have met him at a dinner party somewhere before. Stewart, introduce yourself.”

Stewart stared intently at Liselotte’s fact before bowing deeply. “I’m Stewart Huguenot. Nice to meet you.”

“It’s nice to meet you too,” Liselotte returned the words with a cheery smile. “Now, I shall introduce the representative of my guards as well. This is Aria, who also works as my head attendant.”

Alphonse widened his eyes at Aria’s beauty before speaking. “...I will not stand for you beautiful ladies putting yourselves in danger. There is no need for you to act as escorts — we knights will be sufficient in protecting you...”

Liselotte shook her head with a chuckle. “Thank you for the consideration. However, my attendants are also trained in combat, so we will not fall behind you knights.”

“Hahaha, that is reassuring to hear.” Alphonse laughed heartily, looking at Aria’s slender figure. He didn’t seem to be taking Liselotte’s words seriously.

“...Aria? Aria, you said? Could you be the Governess family’s...” Raymond stared at Aria’s face closely and muttered. Having overheard Raymond’s words, Duke Huguenot spoke up.

“Hmm? Do you know her, Raymond?”

“She’s the daughter of the Viscount Governess’s family. Our fathers are well-acquainted with each other, but I haven’t seen her since we were young...” Raymond said as he stared fixedly at Aria.

“Hmm. No wonder she seemed somewhat familiar...” Duke Huguenot said in comprehension, looking at Aria somewhat suspiciously. He wondered why a noble from Beltrum was serving Liselotte.

“You grew out your hair... I’ve always wondered what you were up to. What happened to your family was, umm, unfortunate... But you were working at the castle after you dropped out of Beltrum’s Royal Academy, right?” Raymond asked with a nervous expression.

“It was difficult for the daughter of a ruined house to stay there, so I quit. I am serving Lady Liselotte now, so I have left my kingdom behind me,” Aria replied simply.

“I see...”

That makes sense... Duke Huguenot accepted with a conflicted face.

Meanwhile, Raymond looked like he wanted to say something as he watched Aria with the same conflicted expression.

Liselotte seemed to notice the air growing heavier. “She’s an extremely talented person, you know? After she ran away and started to work as an adventurer, I scouted her to work for me. She’s now one of my most trusted retainers,” she said proudly.

“Hahaha. I suppose that means our kingdom has regrettably let a special talent go.” Duke Huguenot laughed openly, joining Liselotte in changing the topic.

“Yes, fortunately for me. But under no circumstances would I be willing to return her, sorry to say,” Liselotte said, giggling with a smile.

Since, all joking aside, you really are a special talent. No? She looked over at Aria and gave a small wink.

Thank you very much. Aria smiled in return, letting out a puff of laughter.

◇　◇　◇

After the exchange with Duke Huguenot and his entourage, Liselotte was sent off by Baronet Bochsa. She departed for Amande, accompanied by a large party of Duke Huguenot’s knights and her fully-equipped attendants.

The road through the forest was wide enough for three horse-drawn carriages to pass each other, but the two carriages in their party moved in one line as the knights and attendants surrounded them. The rear carriage held Duke Huguenot, while the front carriage held Liselotte, Flora, Roanna, and Hiroaki.

Hiroaki casually gave a big yawn as he stretched his legs within the carriage. “I’m still sleepy, but it’s nice being rocked by the carriage for once. And this way, I get to chat with you guys in a private room, too.” He looked around at the cute girls accompanying him and smiled with satisfaction.

“You must not let your guard down, Sir Hiroaki.” Roanna pouted her lips slightly as she warned Hiroaki.

“Hey hey, there’s no need to sulk like that, Roanna.” Hiroaki smirked with a huff.

“...I am not sulking. I have no reason to sulk. I am merely worried that Sir Hiroaki will be in danger.” Roanna cutely said in an irritated tone.

“Hahaha, I see, I see. However, I’m here to protect Liselotte, not you guys.” Hiroaki laughed cheerily, patting the head of Roanna beside him. Then, he looked past Liselotte seated diagonally before him and landed his gaze on Flora, who sat across from him.

“...Thank you for your consideration. However, as Roanna says, it would pain me to see the hero in any danger too. Please don’t push yourself too hard.” Liselotte pasted a commendable grin on her face as she replied to Hiroaki.

“Ah, I don’t mind if you’re worried for me, but do I really seem that unreliable to you? I’m still a hero, you know?” Hiroaki’s smile turned bitter as he looked at Liselotte and the others.

“You are, of course, most reliable. However, you don’t like conflict, correct? You don’t want to use your hero powers to kill people. Isn’t this what you told us when we first met?” Roanna said, peering at Hiroaki’s face from the side with a pained expression.

“Did the hero really say such a thing...?” Liselotte widened her eyes slightly in curiosity.

“Ah, you mean when I was first summoned? Now that you mention it, I did say something like that.” Hiroaki got a far look in his eyes as he thought back to the past uncomfortably.

“Out of pure curiosity, I would like to hear more about when you were summoned.” Interested in the topic of his summoning, Liselotte decided to inquire about it somewhat boldly.

“Ah, you want to hear about me? Why, I used to be rather inexperienced in my youth, but if it’s at the request of Liselotte herself, then sure. I’ll tell you,” Hiroaki agreed happily. He started chatting talkatively. “Well, to be honest with you, when I was first summoned into this world, I didn’t know anything. Suddenly, Flora was there, telling me I was a hero or something I didn’t understand. Anyone would be wary, yeah?”

“That must have been quite the ordeal...” Liselotte commented, urging him to continue.

“That being said, I wanted to know what was going on, so I listened to what she had to say. And sure enough, there came the cliche words I had been expecting — that I had been summoned as a hero to help them. They told me Duke Huguenot and the others were in some political struggle with the current government, on the verge of turning into armed conflict. And, well, you’d expect them to be looking for my power to use in war, right?”

“So that’s when you said you didn’t want to use your hero power to kill others,” Liselotte said, grasping the general flow of Hiroaki’s story.

“Yeah. Furthermore, I had no intention of becoming a hero... Until I heard about these girls’ situations and decided I had to be the one to protect them. As I learned about the position of a hero, I realized there were things that I could do in a war other than kill people,” Hiroaki said, looking at Flora and Roanna.

And so he became a hero, exactly how Duke Huguenot wanted, huh? Liselotte thought, but didn’t say out loud.

“That’s wonderful of you,” she praised.

“Don’t say that — it makes me seem like some kind of spoiled child overflowing with a sense of justice. That’s not who I am. I don’t want to be seen as one of those nasty main characters.” Hiroaki waved his hand dismissively, averting his gaze out of embarrassment.

“I don’t believe that’s the case...” Liselotte shook her head.

“Yes, it is exactly as Lady Liselotte says,” Flora approved, and Roanna followed suit.

“With all due respect, I must agree.”

“Ah, don’t misunderstand me here. The reason why I want to avoid killing people is because I believe that is a violation of human rights. In the country I was in, no matter what the circumstance, murder was a sentence to being isolated from society for life. And anyway — what goes around, comes around. Humans tend to be tormented by bad aftertastes or feelings of guilt. Honestly, I look down on the act of killing people too. Even if it were for the sake of the kingdom, I don’t think a hero should perform such an inhumane act,” Hiroaki explained, clearly laying out his values.

“...I see your reasons now,” Liselotte said; a quiet and noncommittal response.

I guess he doesn’t know how many murderers he’s surrounded by right now, then, she was thinking to herself.

“That’s all the more reason as to why I’m worried. It’s not uncommon to be attacked by monsters and beasts on the roads that are far away from civilization. There may even be bandits around.” Roanna clutched Hiroaki’s sleeve coquettishly.

“Nah, I doubt any bandits would attack a group of this size and power. And if it was against a monster or beast, I wouldn’t hold back from using my Yamata no Orochi to eliminate it,” Hiroaki said, a challenging smirk rising onto his face.

“There is no need for Sir Hiroaki to bother lifting a hand at mere monsters or beasts. You should just leave it to the knight escorts,” Roanna said imploringly.

Yes, I’d be grateful for that, too. From Duke Huguenot’s perspective, I guess he wants to see the hero in actual combat? It doesn’t seem like he has any real experience, after all... Liselotte thought, before taking a tired breath.

“However, that’s part of a hero’s duty too, right? To subjugate or show mercy to those who have wronged other people. I have become a hero now. I should experience things like that, too,’ Hiroaki said, sighing with exasperation.

Liselotte decided it was the perfect opportunity to ask Hiroaki of any real combat experience. “...Do you have any experience subduing monsters or beasts, hero?”

“None. Unfortunately, my previous world was rather peaceful. That being said, I won’t cower before a mere monster or beast. I hate any sort of sniveling like that. Well, though they may have wronged people, it still doesn’t feel too good taking their lives...” Hiroaki responded, looking gloomy.

“You really do hold an intense dislike for conflict. Sir Hiroaki, you truly are so kind...” Roanna’s expression darkened as she looked up at Hiroaki’s face.

“It’s fine. I’m in this world right now, after all. My old world is gone. It’s probably necessary for me to lightly experience some real combat and say my true farewells to that other world.” Hiroaki seemed to be completely submerged in his sentimental feelings as he petted Roanna’s head.

“You truly are a wonderful person,” Roanna said, clinging to Hiroaki.

Liselotte sighed quietly to herself, her gaze shifting to Flora sitting beside her. Ugh, I hope we arrive in Amande soon... Hmm? She realized rather belatedly that Flora had been quiet during that entire exchange.

“Princess Flora, how are you feeling? I hope the carriage ride isn’t too uncomfortable for you... Please let me know if you need anything,” she offered out of concern.

“Ah, no, I’m fine. Thank you for your consideration.” Flora gave an uncomfortable smile and shook her head.

“That is good to hear. I couldn’t help but notice you weren’t saying much...” Liselotte said, observing Flora’s face.

“Ah, no, umm. I’m not very good at talking, so I feel calmer just listening to other people talk like this. Everything Sir Hiroaki is saying is new to me, so...” Flora excused herself, smiling bashfully.

“...Oh, I apologize for assuming, then. But would you mind talking to me a little? There is much I would like to hear about from you, if possible.”

“Oh, I would be happy to,” Flora agreed cheerfully. Hiroaki, who had overheard their conversation from where he sat opposite to them, raised an objection.

“Oi oi, don’t forget about us too.”

“...Of course. So, what shall we start with?” Flora would probably speak less with Hiroaki joining the conversation, but Liselotte couldn’t refuse him. She knew she would have to lead the talk and accepted Hiroaki reluctantly.

Interlude: Behind the Departure...

Meanwhile, in Beltrant, the capital of Beltrum; the morning after Rio and Celia had visited Count Claire’s territory...

At the foot of the hill where the Beltrum royal castle stood was a large lake that sustained the water for the entire capital. Next to the lake was a harbor where enchanted airships were anchored.

At present, the Ricca Guild’s enchanted airship was also anchored there, awaiting the boarding of Liselotte, the only daughter of Galarc Kingdom’s great lord Duke Cretia. In a private room on board the enchanted airship, Liselotte impatiently waited for departure as her waiting maid, Aria, poured her a cup of tea. But contrary to her elegant manner of sipping tea, Liselotte sighed wearily.

“Goodness me. We can finally leave...”

After being invited to Celia and Charles’ wedding ceremony, the uproar over the abduction had resulted in her containment in the Beltrum castle’s guest house under the pretext of protection up until last night.

“It’s been four days since the ceremony was suspended. Given how busy your daily life is, my lady, I humbly believe that this was a well-deserved break...” Aria, Liselotte’s close confidant and head maid, said to her in a calm voice.

“But the work will be piled up when we return, you realize? When I think about that mountain of paperwork...” Liselotte muttered with a gloomy face. As the governor of Amande, the president of the Ricca Guild, and the fact she would have been gone a week by the time she returned, just imagining the amount of work piled up had her feeling despondent.

“There’s no helping that. Try not to think about it until we return,” Aria said bluntly.

“...Well, I suppose you have a point. It’s not like I can do any of that work in my current situation.” Liselotte sighed quietly and pouted, her lips sticking out cutely as she slumped her weary body over the table. Seeing that, Aria thought her expression was befitting of a normal fifteen-year-old girl rather than a noble or merchant. Aria giggled at the sight of Liselotte’s true self.

“Lady Liselotte, it’s Chloe!” The voice of a young girl could be heard along with a knock on the door.

Liselotte immediately shot up into a proper posture and gave the girl permission to enter the room. “Come in — you can open the door.”

With a clack, the door opened. “E-Excuse me. I came to report that the preparations to depart have been completed.” Chloe — a cute girl in her early teens, wearing attendants’ clothing — stated her business with a hint of uncomfortable nervousness.

“Got it. Tell them I’m ready to depart at any time. Quickly and safely, that is,” Liselotte said with a nod, smiling gently.

“U-Understood, my lady! Please excuse me!” Chloe bowed deeply and left the room.

“She still seems to be rather nervous,” Liselotte said with a giggle.

“Honestly. Her training period is over now, yet she still has no awareness of herself as a maid.” Aria sighed tiredly.

“Fufu, that’s a newbie for you. And isn’t she just scared of you?” Liselotte said amusedly, turning to Aria. “Even taking that into consideration, her awareness is still lacking,” Aria stated resolutely.

Liselotte chuckled. “My my, how strict of you.”

Several minutes later, the enchanted airship departed from Beltrant’s harbor with Liselotte on board. The wings attached on either side of the sailing airship flapped gently, gradually increasing the speed of the boat along the surface of the water until it lifted off into the air. Its speed accelerated along with the liftoff, causing the ship to soar gently into the sky. At normal operating speed, the airship flew at roughly 50 knots (approximately ninety kilometers per hour).

Today’s weather was clear; the enchanted airship was swathed in bright rays of sunlight as it left the city of Beltrant behind it and flew on eastwards to the Kingdom of Galarc.

Then I guess I shall head off, too.

Reiss, the ambassador of the Proxia Empire, watched the airship. He stood on the surface of the water away from the harbor and gazed up vacantly at the sky.

Interlude: Mii-chan

Meanwhile, in the spirit folk village...

It was early afternoon, and Masato was hard at work training along with Arslan and the others while Miharu and Aki were receiving a spirit arts lesson from Orphia. It hadn’t been long since Miharu, Aki, and Masato had moved to the village — roughly two months had passed since Masato had started receiving sword lessons from Rio.

Spirit arts were an ability that could be learned by any human, but it wasn’t something that could be achieved in a day. Compatibility varied by species, as well as learning time. In order to be able to use the most simplest of spirit arts, a human of the Yagumo region would take roughly a year and a half to two years, whereas a spirit folk child would generally take half a year for the same result. Though, in rare cases, there were exceptions...

“...Ah, I did it!”

Miharu and the other Earth children had shown remarkable progress in these last two months. Miharu, who had been staring fixatedly at the empty air in her outstretched hand, let out a happy cry when a small bubble roughly one centimeter in diameter appeared in her palm.

“Yup, you did it! Your activation time has been growing shorter and shorter every day!” Orphia, who had been standing to the side as her instructor, said in praise. She was just as delighted as Miharu was.

“That’s amazing, Miharu. I’ve only just started being able to detect ode...” Aki, who had been holding her hand outstretched nearby, murmured somewhat enviously. Unlike Miharu, Aki had yet to reach a level where she could activate a spirit art.

Reaching the point of spirit art activation required the acquirement of three skills first — detecting ode, visualizing ode, and detecting mana (of these three, only ode detection was necessary to use magic). In addition, it required the manipulation of ode and conveyance of one’s will into mana, which would normally take a regular human over a year of training.

Miharu was a special case for being able to activate a spirit art in a mere two months, though Aki was also learning spirit arts at an exceptional pace for a human. At her learning rate, she could catch up to Miharu in a few more months.

“Miharu may be amazing, but Aki isn’t losing to most spirit folk in terms of progress either, you know? I don’t know the reason why, but the three of you have an extraordinary amount of magic essence.” Orphia must have heard Aki’s muttering, as she spoke up with some words of encouragement.

“...Essence amount aside, my growth is barely any different compared to Masato, though...” Aki pouted.

“Hmm. That’s because Masato is just as amazing, but I guess it’s hard to feel that when there are no other humans to compare yourselves with,” Orphia said with a bittersweet laugh.

“Speaking of which, how long did it take for Haruto to learn spirit arts?” Aki asked, the question suddenly popping into her mind.

“Ahh, umm... Rio has a contract with Lady Aishia, so he’s a bit of a special case, so to speak...” Orphia replied with some difficulty.

“Was he fast?” Aki asked nervously. Miharu listened to them, curious about the answer too.

“I believe he said he was a child when he was suddenly able to use it one day...” Orphia gave in and replied.

“Wow...” Aki’s eyes widened.

“Yeah...” Miharu was also taken aback with shock.

“But Rio’s case is really one-of-a-kind, so the two of you mustn’t compare yourselves with him, okay? You’re all unique... There’s no need to rush yourselves,” Orphia said the to the two of them, encouraging Aki not to lose confidence.

“...Okay. But I at least want to learn it faster that Masato!” Aki nodded enthusiastically, cheering herself up.

“Hmm. Well, you are siblings. I suppose having a rivalry is a good thing?” Orphia tilted her head, looking at Miharu beside her.

“Yup. They’re close, after all.” Miharu nodded with a smile.

“T-That’s not true!” Aki shook her head furiously out of embarrassment.

“Oho? What’s going on here?”

“Aki’s face is red!”

Latifa and Vera took a break from their nearby training and came over, noticing Aki’s blushing face.

“We were talking about how Aki and Masato are really close siblings,” Miharu replied with a giggle.

“D-Don’t, Miharu!” Aki reddened further and whined.

“I see, I see,” Vera said with a grin, looking at Aki’s face.

“W-We’re not! Maybe with Onii-chan, but definitely not with Masato!” Aki turned away to hide her embarrassment and puffed up her cheeks. If Masato had been present, she would have been even more embarrassed.

“Fufufu. We know, Aki. Right, Latifa?” Vera nodded along, then looked at Latifa.

Latifa grinned widely. “Yeah, that’s right.”

“That look tells me you two definitely don’t get it...” Aki glared at Vera and Latifa reproachfully.

“Ahaha, it’s okay. I’m also really close with my Onii-chan, too. We’re the same!” Latifa said with a carefree smile. Vera also puffed out her chest proudly.

“I love my sister Sara very much, so I’m the same, too!”

“...Hmph. Fine, whatever. It’s true that I’m close with my Onii-chan,” Aki muttered under her breath, hiding her bashfulness.

“Fufu.” Miharu and Orphia exchanged looks before breaking into giggles. Alma and Sara also wandered over from where they had been training nearby.

“Miharu, Orphia — shall we get ready for the cooking class soon?” Alma asked.

“Ah, that’s right. Let’s go, Miharu,” Orphia suggested.

“Okay,” Miharu agreed cheerfully. She had been trying to make the most of her skills to help out the village as much as possible. In order to do that, she had taken over the cooking class Rio had sometimes held for the women of the village. She’d also taken to teaching crafting classes. Orphia was her assistant.

“I’m sure you need as many hands as you can get. We’ll help out, too, so let’s go together,” Sara offered.

Latifa and Vera exchanged glances before immediately jumping in. “We want to go, too!”

◇　◇　◇

Afterwards, Miharu’s group relocated to the village community center. They worked together to prepare for their cooking class in a large food preparation room.

The women of the village gradually gathered, and the class commenced without incident. The participants were split into groups in order to create cream tart cakes, which was the recipe of the day. Despite being nervous about her instructor role, Miharu worked with Orphia to teach the village women. Time passed in the blink of an eye.

“Now, it’s time to try it!”

They moved to the community cafeteria to taste the results. Vera’s wolf ears and tail shook from side to side as she gazed at the sliced cakes expectantly.

“Hurry up, Miharu! Quickly!” Latifa was urging Miharu to cut the cakes faster.

“Smells good...” While Aki wasn’t rushing anyone else, she did stare at the apple cake with intense longing.

Miharu giggled with amusement as she sliced the cakes with a careful hand. “Wait just a little longer.” After serving the cake to the younger ones first, she then went on to place a slice of cake each on a plate for Sara, Orphia, Alma, and herself. During that time, Orphia prepared tea for everyone. With that, it was finally time dig in.

“Thank you for the food!” they all said before trying the cake.

“Ooooh!” Latifa, Vera, and Aki all looked extremely satisfied with the result.

“Yup, this is very delicious.” Sara also took a bite of cake before nodding happily.

“When everyone works together, it tastes even better,” Alma said with a smile.

“It’s rather fun cooking and eating in a different environment than where we normally are. The people who joined the class also seemed to have fun, so it’s all thanks to Miharu.” Orphia nodded along, smiling at Miharu. The other tables in the cafeteria were occupied by village women who chatted amicably while enjoying their cake.

“Huh, me?” Miharu was taken by surprise and widened her eyes.

“Yup. It’s all thanks to Miharu taking over the instructor role from Rio that this class could resume,” Orphia replied immediately.

“Ahaha, I don’t know if I can make a good substitute for Haruto, but if it helps the village out even a little, then I’m glad.” Miharu grinned a little unsurely.

“This is much more than just a little. Everyone looks forward to Miharu’s cooking classes.”

“Yes, please have more confidence in yourself.”

Both Sara and Alma spoke up to encourage Miharu.

Vera nodded along. “That’s right! Miharu’s cooking is just as delicious as Rio’s cooking. The seasoning is just slightly different, but that’s because they’re foods from Rio’s hometown in the Yagumo region, right?”

“...Yeah. Though there are some Strahl foods too,” Miharu nodded uncomfortably. While Latifa and the older girls had been present at the discussion about bringing Miharu and the others into the village, Vera didn’t know they were from another world. She still believed they were from the same town as Rio.

“I see. There are some foods that are similar to our village, but there are lots of foods in the world that we don’t know about, too. It’s really been a good thing that Rio and Miharu came to our village!” Vera hummed in appreciation before beaming with a happy expression.

“Fufu, thank you. I’m also very grateful I was able to come to this village and meet all of you. It’s all thanks to Haruto.” Miharu smiled happily as she spoke.

“Yes! It’s thanks to Rio that I was able to become friends with Latifa, so Rio really is our savior!” Vera looked at Latifa and nodded enthusiastically.

Latifa smiled cheerfully, returning Vera’s gaze. “Ehehe.”

“...It’s true that if Rio hadn’t been there, we would have never been able to meet with Latifa nor Miharu or Aki like this. When you think of it that way, it’s kinda miraculous.” Sara muttered sentimentally.

Latifa giggled. “Looking back now, the first time Onii-chan and I visited the village, we had no idea what would happen,” she said with amusement.

“Guh...” In contrast, Sara, Orphia, and Alma all looked rather guilty.

Aki watched the exchange between the spirit folk girls in silence, suddenly remembering the past. Come to think of it, back when Masato first received Rio’s approval of his warrior training, Alma said something in the hot springs... About how the first time Haruto and Latifa wandered into the forest, she had chills fighting him just like when she was watching the warrior training.

Back then, she had been able to catch a rare glimpse of the cold side of Rio. Now, she was completely distracted by thoughts of that interaction, making her curious about what happened in the past.

“...Now that I think about it, Latifa was brought to this village by Rio too, right? What happened back then?” Aki asked nervously.

Latifa pondered over where to begin. “Hmm. Well, to sum it up, Onii-chan was mistaken for a kidnapper and thrown into a jail...”

“Huh?! Really?!” Aki’s eyes widened in shock. Miharu also turned her attention towards them in surprise.

“Yup. Umm, the elders have told you why the people of this village live far away from humans, right? So we always have a barrier put up around the village for warding away humans,” Latifa said, beginning with an explanation of the backstory.

“Ah, did you end up fighting because you entered the barrier without permission, or something?” Aki asked, taking a guess.

“Yeah. It was around four years ago, I think. We crossed the barrier without realizing it and were camping in the forest when we were attacked. I was asleep, so I was already carried to the village by the time I woke up...” Latifa said, reminiscing. The countless barriers that stretched around the village were all of a very high quality. At that time, Rio still hadn’t learned the ways of spirit arts properly, so while he was able to ignore the effects of the barrier and pass through, he hadn’t noticed its activation.

Aki was taken aback before hesitantly looking over at Sara and the other girls. “Were Sara and the others there, too?”

Sara nodded regretfully. “...Yes. When we saw Latifa sleeping, we mistook her for an abducted village child and ambushed Rio. There was no excusing our actions.”

Orphia and Alma also recalled that time with sullen expressions.

Aki must have felt the air getting heavier as she spoke up in a hurry. “B-But the misunderstanding was cleared up, right? You’re all as close as family now. I’m a little curious about what series of events led to that happening with everyone.”

“...Yes, we noticed the misunderstanding itself immediately. Rio had traveling equipment for both himself and Latifa, after all...” Sara explained hesitantly.

“It was in the middle of the night, but we hurriedly reported it to Elder Ursula when we realized Latifa might not be from here. She got angry and ordered us to release him immediately, so Alma and I headed to the jail cells, I believe...” Orphia continued.

“...Yes,” Alma agreed heavily as she recalled. “But the jail was freezing cold and Rio had passed out in only a thin layer of clothing, so his body was completely chilled. He didn’t even twitch when we called out to him, so we were pretty panicked for a while there, thinking he had died.”

“Ahaha. Alma was quite panicked at the time. She was rushing to check that he was still breathing.” Orphia reflected on the bitter memory and smiled faintly.

“I-I wasn’t that panicked... But I was worried,” Alma explained herself with embarrassment.

“Fufu. You were so relieved when you were able to confirm he was still breathing. Then, we tried to wake him by shaking him, but Rio just wouldn’t wake up...” Orphia said.

“...Come to think of it, Rio was muttering something in his sleep. When he woke up, he also seemed to coming out of some kind of dream, all dazed and stuff...” Alma noted.

“Ah, right. Yeah, he seemed rather disappointed when he saw our faces, almost like he wasn’t seeing us. His expression was really sad too...” Orphia also seemed to have remembered Rio’s face at the time, as she looked rather conflicted. Just what kind of impression did she have of Rio at the time?

“...Something like that happened?” Latifa’s eyes widened in interest. Miharu, Aki, and Sara had also been listening silently, looking at Orphia and Alma with gazes of deep curiosity.

“Yeah. If I’m not mistaken, I think he cried a little. Maybe he met someone in his dream? If so, we may have done something awful when we forcefully woke him up...” Orphia spoke about her complicated feelings regarding the past with a shameful expression.

“...What did Onii-chan say at that time?” Latifa couldn’t help but ask.

“Umm, I don’t know what it was about, but... It sounded something like yattoaeta or miichan, maybe?” Orphia answered to the best of her ability. Naturally, she didn’t know what those sounds meant; the words Orphia had heard Rio utter were Japanese words, after all — the words for I finally met you and Mii-chan.

“Eh...?” For Miharu, whose mother tongue was Japanese, Orphia’s words made her heart skip a beat.

Aki and Latifa — the latter of whom was hiding the fact she had memories of her past life — both twitched in interest as well.

Sara noticed the change in Miharu’s expression and called out to her curiously. “Is something the matter, Miharu?”

“Ah... Nope. It’s nothing.” Miharu kept a smile on her face as she shook her head.

...There’s no way. Haruto said he was a university student anyway, she told herself.

However, an indescribable feeling squeezed around her heart, which was thudding away for some reason. She couldn’t get Rio — no, Haruto — out of her head.

But then, she noticed how Aki was staring at her. “Hm?” Miharu pasted an awkward smile on her face and tilted her head.

“...” For a brief moment, Aki’s face twisted with a terribly bitter expression before she immediately averted her eyes.

Could Miharu have... And what... was Aki’s face just now? Latifa had been secretly observing the two of them. She knew that Haruto used to call Miharu by the nickname “Mii-chan,” which was why her instincts immediately considered the meaning behind Aki’s brief expression. She wondered if it was possible they had made the association with Haruto.

But there weren’t enough hints as to what was really going on. All Latifa had heard from Rio in the past was that Amakawa Haruto’s parents divorced because of his mother’s infidelity, leaving a young Haruto and Aki to go their separate ways. There was no way for Latifa to know how Miharu felt about Amakawa Haruto now, much less Aki’s unawareness of the reason for her parents divorce or her complex emotions towards Haruto and a father that she had no blood relation to. There wasn’t enough evidence for her to come to a sensible conclusion about Aki’s expression. Even if Latifa could imagine such an answer, she had no way of confirming it since she was hiding her own previous memories from Miharu and everyone else.

But, even so...

I want to know. Latifa grinded her teeth in frustration. She wanted to lay bare everything she knew about Miharu, Aki, and Amakawa Haruto. She wanted to talk to them about it all.

But she couldn’t. Rio had stopped her. There was no way Latifa would disobey Rio’s words by going behind his back, no matter how distressed it made her feel.

The most she could do was come up with a question that pressed the core of the matter in a roundabout way, and watch for the reaction. “...Mii-chan, huh? I wonder what it means. Right, Miharu?” Latifa kept a smile on her face as she fearfully addressed Miharu, who was sitting beside her.

“Y-Yeah. Who knows?” Miharu tilted her head with a somewhat unnatural smile.

This reaction... She really does remember Onii-chan after all, doesn’t she? Latifa deduced. She also shot a glance in Aki’s direction, who had a faint wrinkle in her brow and an obviously sour expression on her face.